I want to open it up... on a sunny day, I want to run with it open.
Stylish, isn't it? I wish I could watch it.
Wow!
I'm going to buy a car! Yay!
Hi, I'm Suzuka Tomita from Hyugaizaka46!
Thank you for watching the first episode of "Tomita Buying a Car", which has now reached over a million views.
I may have mentioned last time that I would like to see some sports cars.
Today, I'm here at GT Garage!
Oh! It's sunny!
Last time it rained, so we had to do it in the rain with umbrellas.
I'm looking forward to seeing a lot of sports cars today! Thank you very much for your cooperation!
Let's go!
If you have any questions, please feel free to contact me.
I'll ask the manager...
I'll ask the manager if there's anything I don't understand.
I'd like to take a look at it.
I don't know much about the sports department.
I don't know much about motorsports.
I've been working in the field of motorsports.
I do reports and go to circuits.
There, you know, there are a lot of good sports departments.
Oh, this one...
This is GR.
GR Yaris
Is it red?
It's quite compact, isn't it?
More than I expected.More than I thought.
Yes, but
It looks compact and quite wide.
I see
Really.
A sports car, after all.
Oh, wow.
I don't know, maybe it's something.
I might take them more seriously than I did the last time I looked at SUVs.
I might take sports cars more seriously than I did the last time I looked at an SUV.
Wow! Supra!
Look at this rear wing!
This is so cool! Isn't this so cool?
Don't you think it's cool when you see a car with this on the highway?
You don't see them very often.
Do people who drive on circuits put this kind of thing on their cars?
Yes, they do. They are parts that stabilize the car when the speed increases.
It is not used for normal driving.
Was this a long time ago?
This is in the Heisei period.
What year is Heisei?
Let's see... 12 years.
Twelve years! What? What? That means I was born in 2001.
So we're about the same age, right?
That's right.
What? Isn't that kind of a good example?
Isn't it nice to buy a car of your birth year
It's kind of nice to buy a car of your birth year.
But I guess...
I wonder if it's about this low.
It's pretty low, isn't it?It's pretty low, isn't it?
I'm so freaked out.
Look at this, folks.
Everyone who loves cars knows this.
AE86.
It's the one from Initial D, right?
Wow, doesn't it look perfect with my outfit today?
Pair it with my outfit today.
Lovely.
I'd like to drive one of these old cars someday.
I'd like to drive one of these old cars.
It's a little bit dizzying, isn't it?
I'm so giddy with the appearance of these wonderful cars.
S2000
Wow!
Isn't that it?
This is the first convertible car I've ever seen!
So cool!
Let's get a closer look.
Oh, no!
Isn't the seat awesome?
Sexy!
It's so cool!
Excuse me.
May I try this S2000?
Sure, of course.
Wow.
I've never driven a convertible before.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
Wow.Wow.
Firm.
Wow.
Hey.
LOL.
Car alarm sound
Open.
Excuse me, I just heard the security alarm.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Car alarm sounds
I think the car rejected me.
It's okay. Excuse me.
Don't get in the car.
To Snissen.
Sorry.
LOL.
Well, excuse me.
Car alarm sound
Oh, hey
Scary, scary, sinking in
Oh, it's so nice!
Wait a minute. I'm going to want one when I get in.
Front... Front...
Back. It stays down.
Okay...
It's locked in.
Oh, wow.
It's pretty much the same when you close it.
It's like I'm in my own space.I feel like I'm in my own space.
I feel like I'm in my own space.
Let's open it.
It stopped halfway.
Wow.
Ugh.
Ew.
Wow. I want to open it up.
I'd love to run in the sun. It's so cool. Thank you.
I wonder how much it costs.
It's way over my budget.
Not at all.
But buying this for the first car is pretty crazy, isn't it?
I know, right?
Amazing! It's very tasteful. Thank you.
Wow!
It's so cool.
It makes me feel like I'm at my grandpa's house.
It makes me feel safe. It's so relaxing and cool.
Wow, isn't it stylish?
It's stylish.
This is the main hall.
Wasn't this like this in all of grandpa's houses?
It's still going to take an hour and a half today.
Take your time.
All right, let's move on.
Wow.
Wow, it looks like a sports car.
Isn't that sideways really wide?
GTR.
NISSANNissan
Nissan's
Wow, eh.
It's so much more luxurious.
Ooh.
Aww.
Wow.
It's really sinking in.
There's a seat in the back.
There's a seat in the back, too.
Wow, it seats four.
And there's a speaker in the middle.
That's great.
I want to turn the wheel one more time.
What do you think?
How is it?
Yeah, it's solid.
That's great. You want me to swing it around?
It's gotta be tight, right?
Mm-hmm.
Huh.
Oh!
What's this? Oh, 86, GR86.
What's that? What does that mean?
That's a BRZ.
BRZ. That's the BRZ, right? Like sisters.
Yes, siblings.
Brother and sister.
This one's from Toyota, this one's from Subaru.
Thank you.Wow. Thank you.
Yes. Excuse me.
Oh!
I like it. - Oh, it's not sporty at all.
I can ride these pedals in my everyday life.
It looks totally fine.
Nice!
Hey, look
Look at this Civic Type R
It's discontinued now. It's very popular.
I'd get so excited if I saw one in a parking lot in town.
I always tell my mom, "Look, look, look!
It's so cool!
And this one, too. They've taken aerodynamics into consideration.
They made the air so it's clear.
Exhale... Exhale from there.
This part is also designed to let air in.
It's so cool!
Even the tires are red with the Honda logo.
I'm talking to you as if someone were here.
Look how stylish it is!
I wish I could watch you guys for the rest of my life.
Good night.
This is so cool!
I love it.
Yes, well, the Civic Type R is now only available in manual form.
Yes, it is.
Manual is the only way to drive a cool car.
Manual is the only way to drive a cool car, right?
It's not within your budget, is it?
That's right.I know, right?
What do we do now?
Ladies and gentlemen...
Is there such a thing as a bright yellow S2000?
This is stock yellow.
Stock yellow?
So cute!
What?
NSX?
It's an NSX, ladies and gentlemen.
Wow.
It's a little bit gray.
Oh, wow...
They're all so cool.
I'm an automatic driver and my license doesn't allow me to drive a manual car, but I wanted to see one in action.
I'd be happy to give you a ride... if you sit in the girls' seat next to me.
Really? Please let me ride with you.
Please do.
I'd like to ride in this Toyota GR Yaris.
I'll be in the passenger seat.
Let's go!
Here we go!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Aww.
Ooh!
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh.
Wow Yoo-hoo!
Aww.
Yay!
Wow!Wow!
Ooh! Ho-ho-ho!
Wow!
Whoo-hoo!
Oh, so it's a sport.
Oh, my gosh.
I can feel it...
Vibration...
It's like there's a vibration or something.
Hmmm...
Wow, that was fun!
Thank you so much!
I'm home.
Hmm...
It felt like a sports car.
I guess it's a little harder than my normal car.
A little bit harder than my normal car. Yes, it is.
Oh!
It feels so good to open the car for the first time.
It feels so good!
There's nothing to block my view.
Wow!
Feels good.
Here we go.
Ooh!
Oh! Not even close!
What?What?
No! The stability when accelerating was a bit amazing.
It was amazing! I was so surprised!
It felt like it was floating straight up.
It feels like it's running.
It's not just a car that looks good.
It's also a fun car to drive.
I want to drive along the coast.
Yes, a convertible
Very nice, a convertible.
Great!
It was great! Thank you very much.
Wow! Great!
Ha! They have totally different qualities, both of them.
But there is something about a convertible
My orientation is a little higher because you can open and close it
Because you can open it and close it.
You can open it and you can close it.
Oh!
What's this?
Supra.
Thank you very much.
Come again.
I'm so lost.
I don't know if I can...
I don't know if I can choose a car.
So...
Today I...
Suzuka Tomita
a car.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom!Boom, boom, boom, boom!
I'm buying!
I'm going to buy a sports car for 1,000 yen, but I think it's still too expensive for me to buy my first sports car, but I really want to drive a sports car someday.
Also, after seeing the A86 today, I've become interested in old cars.
I would like to go see old cars too, and I will definitely buy a car.
If you enjoyed today's video, please subscribe to the channel and click the "Good" button.
Bye bye!
Thank you so much for your time today.
I'm glad you enjoyed the day so much.